L00: '# Week 1 Day 1'
L01: ''
L02: '## READING WISELY'
L03: ''
L04: 'The youngster who reads voraciously, though indiscriminately, does not necessarily gain in wisdom over the teenager who is more selective in his reading choices. A young man who has read the life story of every eminent athlete of the twentieth century, or a coed who has steeped herself in every social-protest novel she can get her hands on, may very well be learning all there is to know in a very limited area. But books are replete with so many wonders that it is often discouraging to see bright young people limit their own experiences.'
L05: ''
L06: '## NEW WORDS'
L07: ''
